A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Fellowships, Administration Files, SG 2 FA1226
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Fellowships, Administration Files, SG 2
1925-2000
1990-1999
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1226
167.51 Cubic Feet 127 standard record storage boxes and 3 document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Records remain in order as physically received.
Arranged in four series as follows:
Series 1: Harkness Fellowships: Administration.
Series 2: Atlantic Fellowships.
Series 3: Ian Axford Fellowships.
Series 4: International Health Policy Program (IHP) Administration.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund archives, along with all subsequent additions tot he collection, were donated to Rockefeller Archive Center in 1985. Records were transferred to RAC by Commonwealth Fund in multiple accessions spanning 1988-2001.
Scope and Contents
Contains administrative records for the Harkness Fellowships, with a limited volume of files pertaining to the Atlantic Fellowships in Public Policy, and the Ian Axford Fellowships in Public Policy.
Files primarily consist of preparatory and planning documentation for associated conferences, workshops, seminars, orientation packets and handbooks. Records also include IHP chronological files and general correspondence as well as general administrative fellows files.
- Harkness Fellowships - Administration, 1
  - Program Flyers and Applications - Australia, 1994, 1996, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Program Flyers and Applications - New Zealand, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
  - Program Flyers and Applications - United Kingdom, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Program Flyers and Applications - General, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Program Flyers and Applications - Financial Times Applications, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Harkness Fellowship Handbook, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Confidential material
  - Void AIP Forms, 1981-1989 (Box 2)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Invoices and Applications for Coverage of Fellows, 1987-1997 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence with Internal Revenue Service, 1980s (Box 2)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program Reference Guide, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brookings Institution - Washington Seminar on Understanding Federal Operations and Seminar Books, 1991-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2-6)
  - Fellows Information, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Orientation Program, 1990, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 9-13)
  - Orientation Seminar Files, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Reporting Seminar, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Austin Conference, 1992 February (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Planning Meeting, 1996 June-July (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Insurance - Cigna Insurance Book, 1987-1992 (Box 4)
  - Insurance - Harkness Fellowship Program 20-20 Book, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Insurance - Payment Requests, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Internal Revenue Service and Tax Clearance Files files, 1984-1992 (Box 5)
  - Harkness Fellowships- Applications, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
  - Programs, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Seminars, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 28-36)
  - Insurance - Cigna Invoices, 1990-1996 (Box 8)
  - Insurance - Cigna Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 8)
  - Insurance - Payment Requests, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Finance - London Statements, 1992-1995 (Box 8)
  - Fellow's Files and Applications - United Kingdom, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fellow's Files and Applications - Australia, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
  - Fellow's Files and Applications - New Zealand, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fellow's Files and Applications - United Kingdom, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6-16)
  - Fellow's Files - Second Year Plan, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Fellow's Files - End of Tenure Reports, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
  - Fellows Administration Files, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Harkness Fellows - IRS Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Administration, 1988 January-November (Box 12, Folder 1-11)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Administration, 1988 November (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Columbia University, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Georgetown University, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Harvard University, 1967-1986 (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
  - Lehigh University, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1968, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - New York University, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Nieman Foundation for Journalism of Harvard Univeristy, 1950-1985 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Northwestern University, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Oklahoma State University, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Oregon State University, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Princeton University, 1975-1987 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco Art Institute, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Stanford University, 1969-1987 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - University of California, Berkeley and other campuses, 1971-1987 (Box 12, Folder 29-31)
  - University of Chicago, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - University of Iowa, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - University of Michigan, 1974, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, 1974, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1970-1984 (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
  - University of Texas, Arlington, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Washington University in St. Louis, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Yale University, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - United Kingdom Fellows - Interviews, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Berk, Celia, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Events - Visit to Australia and New Zealand, 1978, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Events - Dinner for Messrs. Blainey and Hinde, 1983 January 4 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Events - Goldberg, Mary - Visit, 1983 April 25-May 11 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Events - Dinner for the Plowdens, 1984 May 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Events - Merrison, Alec - Tour through the United States, 1986 March 24-April 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Events - Visit to London - Atherton, Alfred L., Margaret E. Mahoney and Gail Potter Neale, 1986 January 26-31 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Events - Visit to London - Atherton, Alfred L., Margaret E. Mahoney, John Craig and Sims Farr, 1986 November 26-December 3 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Events - Visit to United Kingdom - Atherton, Alfred L., Celia Beck and Gail Potter Neale, 1987 January 26-February 14 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Events - Warnock, Mary - Tour through the United States, 1987 March 16-30 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Events - Dinner for Mary Warnock, 1987 March 17 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Events - Reception for J. Terry Larkin, Washington, D. C., 1987 May 26 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Events - Meeting of Departing Fellows, New York, 1987 May (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Events - 1987 Harkness Fellows Orientation, 1987 August 26-27 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Events - Visit to London - Atherton, Alfred L. - Reception, Cambridge, 1987 November 15-16 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Events - Visit to United Kingdom - Atherton, Alfred L., John Craig, Sims Farr and Margaret E. Mahoney, 1987 November 25-December 5 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Events - Visit to United Kingdom - Atherton, Alfred L., John Craig, William Plowden, 1988 January-February (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Events - West Coast Trip - Atherton, Alfred L., and Betty W. Atherton, 1988 February 18-28 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Awards Lists, 1963-1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - End of Tenure Reports, 1981-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2-5)
  - Directory of Fellows Administration Files, 1954-1955, 1968-1977, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 6-12)
  - Application Documentation, 1977, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter - Hark, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Evaluations, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence - Dainton, Frederick, 1973-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - General Correspondence - Duff, James, 1954-1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence - Flint, F. T., 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence - Goldring, Mary, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence - Hetherington, Hector, 1954-1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence - Hill, G. T. R., 1950-1956 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence - Hogg, Christopher, 1979-1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence - Murray, Alice Rosemary, 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence - Murray, Keith, 1955-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence - Newton, Quigg, 1963-1981 (Box 15, Folder 12-16)
  - General Correspondence - Nixon, Edwin R., 1976-1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence - Thistlethwaite, Frank, 1974-1982, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence - Trend, Burke, 1974-1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence - Wass, Douglas, 1978-1985 (Box 15, Folder 20-21)
  - General Correspondence - Whitby, Lionel, 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence - United Kingdom Committee of Award - General Administration, 1973-1988 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence - Dainton, Frederick, 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence - Goldring, Mary, 1980-1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence - Hogg, Christopher, 1980-1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence - Murray, Rosemary, 1977-1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence - Merrison, Alec, 1982-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence - Nixon, Edwin R., 1976-1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence - Plowden, William Julius Lowthian, 1980-1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence - Warnock, Mary, 1983-1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence - Weiss, Douglas, 1958-1960, 1978-1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Orientation and Program Files, 1988-1993 (Box 16, Folder 12-19)
  - Christmas Letter to the Fellows, 1947-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1-8)
  - Handbook for the Harkness Fellowship, 1933-1988 (Box 18, Folder 9-15)
  - Commonwealth Fund Historical Sketches, Program Summaries and Reviews, 1925-1983 (Box 18, Folder 16-22)
  - Program Description, Handbook, Background Material, Seminar Files and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 1-17)
  - Bi-Monthly Report, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Project Updates, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Mid-Year Meeting Program, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Orientation Program, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 5-7)
  - Reporting Seminar Programs, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Princeton Seminar Program, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Austin Program, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Reporting Seminar, Washington, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Final Reporting Seminar, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Staff Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Executive Summaries of Draft Reports, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Fellow Information, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Harkness Reports (Harkness Herald, Harkness Newsletter, HARK, Harkness Bulletin), 1990-1996 (Box 23, Folder 16-18)
  - Seminar Programs, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 19-21)
  - Orientation Program, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Reporting Seminar, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Orientation Program, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Reporting Seminar, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Orientation Program, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Seminar Program, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Reference Guide, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Handbook for Mid-Career Harkness Fellows (Australia and New Zealand), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 29-31)
  - Public Policy and International Affairs Publications and Books (Box 24)
  - Fellowship Applicants - United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand - Short-Listed - Not Selected, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1-9)
  - Reference Guide, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
  - Harkness Fellowship Handbook - United Kingdom, 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 5-8)
  - Harkness Fellowship Handbook - Australia and New Zealand, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 9-12)
  - Harkness Fellowship Handbook - Mid-Career Fellows - United Kingdom, Australia and New Zealand, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 13-15)
  - Gifts-in-Lieu - A-Z, 1968-1986 (Box 27, Folder 1-14)
  - Evaluations, 1979-1982 Fellows, 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 15-18)
  - Accommodation Survey, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Emoluments Dispersments, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Charts, 1979-1983 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Form Letters, 1969-1984 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Forms and Memoranda, 1980-1984 Fellows, 1980-1985 (Box 27, Folder 23-27)
  - 1969 Tax Reform Act - Clippings and Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Department of State, 1952-1982 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - IRS Publications - Historical, 1952-1978 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Placement, 1970-1983 (Box 27, Folder 31-33)
  - Fellowship Rosters, 1979-1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - US Travel - 1982-1983 Fellows, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Directory of Fellows 1975 and 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Fellows, Trip Reports, 1964-1984 (Box 28, Folder 3-8)
  - Dinners, Events, Reports and Correspondence, 1973-1986 (Box 28, Folder 9-20)
  - Exchange Program, 1989-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
  - 1990 Directory of Fellows Administration Files, 1989-1993 (Box 30, Folder 4-11)
  - Harkness Report Files (Harkness Newsletter, Harkness Bulletin), 1989-1993 (Box 30, Folder 13-27)
  - Financial Records (Box 31)
  - Retirement Reception Files (Box 31)
  - London Office Files (Box 31)
  - Finances and Expenses (Box 31)
  - Harkness Fellowship Management Files and Job Descriptions (Box 31)
  - Correspondence with IRS, 1990s (Box 31)
  - Harkness Fellowship Mailing Lists, 1989-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
  - United Kingdom, Select Committee (Advisory) Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
  - Wearne Associates Activity Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
  - Housing, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Tag Sale, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Merchandise and Merchandising, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 10-18)
  - Marketing, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Christmas Cards, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 20-21)
  - Outcome Index, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 23-24)
  - Press Releases, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - United Kingdom Advisory Committee, Members, 1985-1995 (Box 32, Folder 26-39)
  - Visits by Committee Members, 1991-1995 (Box 32, Folder 40-47)
  - Financial Times Fellowships files and Advisory Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 48-49)
  - Harvard University, 1989-1994 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Howard University, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - University of Minnesota, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - ICMA, 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - ICF, Inc., 1990 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - University of Illinois, Chicago, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Indiana University, Center on Philanthropy, 1992-1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Indiana University, 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Public Administration (IPA), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 14-15)
  - University of Texas, Arlington, LBJ School of Public Affairs, 1988-1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - University of Maryland, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Mental Health Policy Resource Center, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - University of Michigan, School of Social Work, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - University of Minnesota, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - MIT, Program for Senior Executives (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - National Governors Association, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - National Association of Partners in Education, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Fellowships Seminar, Atlanta, GA, 1992, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 27-38, 42)
  - New Zealand and Austalian Embassy ReceptionFiles, 1991-1994 (Box 33, Folder 39-41)
  - Harkness Fellowship United Kingdom Orientation Files, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 43-45)
  - Harkness Fellowship - Fellows Administration Files, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 46-47)
  - Duke Seminar, 1991 April 13-17 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Brookings Institute files, 1991-1994 (Box 34, Folder 3-22)
  - Selection Process and Interview Files, 1991-1994 (Box 34, Folder 23-26)
  - Post Fellowship Activities, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Post-Tenure Meetings, 1991, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Continental Fellows, 1988-1994 (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
  - Re-entry, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 1991 and 1992 Fellows Reunions, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
  - Seminar for Harkness Fellows, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Potential Academic Hosts, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Placement, 1989-1995 (Box 35, Folder 11-13)
  - US Panel, 1994 March (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Political Economy Research Center, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Princeton University, Woodrow Wilson School of Government, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 16-17)
  - The New School, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - New York University, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Rutgers University, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Ramapo College, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - The Rand Graduate School of Public Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Stanford University, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 23-25)
  - University of North Carolina, School of Social Work, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - University of Pennsylvania, School of Nursing, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - University of South Carolina, School of Social Work, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Tickets, 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Christmas Card Lists, 1993-1996 (Box 36, Folder 3-5)
  - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Fellows Travel Files, 1995-1997 (Box 36, Folder 8-23)
  - Commonwealth Fund Program-Related Activities, 1989-1992 (Box 36, Folder 24-30)
  - 75th Anniversary Celebration of the Commonwealth Fund, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - United Kingdom Conference, 1991 October 16-18 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Commonwealth Fund Management, 1987-1992 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Australian Fellowships - Selection Files, 1991-1995 (Box 37, Folder 1-6)
  - Australian Fellowships - Administrative Files, 1980-1995 (Box 37, Folder 7-22)
  - Australian Fellowships - Finances and General Information, 1975-1993 (Box 37, Folder 23-40)
  - Australian Fellowships - Conference and Seminar Files, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 41-44)
  - Australian Fellowships - Publications, 1979-1994 (Box 37, Folder 45-48)
  - Administrative Correspondence and Reports, 1995, 1996 April-December (Box 38, Folder 1-10)
  - Administrative Correspondence and Reports, 1984-1995 (Box 39, Folder 1-28)
  - Orientation and Seminar Files, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 29-32)
  - Orientation and Seminar Files, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 1-8)
  - Visits, Mentors, Academic Hosts, Conference and Seminar Files, 1989-1994 (Box 40, Folder 9-28)
  - Conference and Seminar Files, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
  - Internships and Procedure Files, 1989-1991 (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
  - Selection Process Files, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 7-14)
  - Expert Assessors, 1989-1995 (Box 41, Folder 15-21)
  - Basic Instructions for Harkness Directory Upkeep, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 22-23)
  - Tax Issues, 1986-1989 (Box 41, Folder 24-26)
  - Finances and Expenses - London and Miscellaneous, 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 27-30)
  - 1990 Survey of Fellows - A-J (Box 42, Folder 1-13)
  - 1990 Survey of Fellows - K-Z (Box 43, Folder 1-14)
  - Tax Files, 1987-1991 (Box 44)
  - Immigrant and Customs Information, 1989-1991 (Box 44)
  - Maps and Travel Information, 1992-1994 (Box 44)
  - Blacklisted Fellows, 1978-1988 (Box 44)
  - Reporting Seminar Files, United States, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 1-29)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - McLean, Margot (New Zealand), 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Morrison, John Clive (United Kingdom), 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 4-6)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - New, Michelle Jennifer Claire (United Kingdom), 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 7-9)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Ridley, Andrew (United Kingdom), 1995-1997 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Salama, Peter (Australia), 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Sears, Heather Jane (United Kingdom), 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 13-15)
  - Responses, Comments and Notes, 1988-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1-4)
  - Subject Files - Education, 1986-1993 (Box 48, Folder 5-13)
  - Subject Files - Children, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Subject Files - Cities, 1987-1991 (Box 48, Folder 15-20)
  - Subject Files - Elderly, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 21-23)
  - Subject Files - Families, 1980-1989 (Box 48, Folder 24-25)
  - Subject Files - Government, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Subject Files - Urban Society and Environment, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Subject Files - Science and Policy, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Subject Files - Health, 1987-1993 (Box 48, Folder 29-32)
  - Subject Files - Housing, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 33-35)
  - Subject Files - Employment, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 36-37)
  - Subject Files - Poverty, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 38-39)
  - Subject Files - Law and Order, 1986-1993 (Box 48, Folder 40-41)
  - Subject Files - Minorities, 1989-1991 (Box 48, Folder 42-43)
  - Subject Files - Grant Making, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Subject Files - Volunteerism, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 45-46)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1934, 1963-1991 (Box 49, Folder 1-20)
  - London Office - Cancelled Fellowships - A-Z, 1956-1987 (Box 50, Folder 1-35)
  - Harkness Report Files (Fellows News), 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1-8)
  - Memoranda - General, 1993 October-1994 September (Box 51, Folder 9-10)
  - Chronological Office Files, 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 11-20)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Selection Committee Meeting, 1995 February 11-12 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Buchan, James McDonald, 1996-1998 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Clark, Lindy Phillipa, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Davies, Robin John, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Forna, Aminatta Satha, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Graham, Kathryn Jane, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Juss, Satvinder Singh, 1996-1998 (Box 52, Folder 9-10)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Keenan, Anthony William, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 11-12)
  - 1996 Fellows Administration Files - Kibblewhite, Andrew Lance, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - London Office - Administrative Files, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
  - London Office - Fellows Reports, 1974-1988 (Box 54, Folder 3-6)
  - London Office - Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
  - London Office - English, Martha M., 1976 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - London Office - Merrison, Alec Watson, 1982-1989 (Box 54, Folder 10-13)
  - London Office - Plowden, William, 1980-1988 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - London Office - Trend, Burke St. John, 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - London Office - Commonwealth Fund Forum, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 16-19)
  - London Office - Johnston, Robert L., 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 20-21)
  - London Office - Administration - Committee Member Correspondence, 1925-1985 (Box 55, Folder 1-21)
  - Receipts and Expenditures, 1978 June-1982 June (Box 56, Folder 1-50)
  - Payments of Non-Degree Candidates, 1974-1978 (Box 56, Folder 51-55)
  - New York Office - Administration - Executive Committee and Awards Committee Files, 1923-1977 (Box 56, Folder 56- 66)